{
    "quiz math level 1": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "4+6= ?",
            "options": [
                11,
                8,
                10,
                9
            ],
            "answer": 10
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "13-10= ?",
            "options": [
                2,
                4,
                1,
                3
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "15-6= ?",
            "options": [
                7,
                8,
                9,
                10
            ],
            "answer": 9
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "6-7= ?",
            "options": [
                -2,
                -1,
                -3,
                0
            ],
            "answer": -1
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "8+4= ?",
            "options": [
                10,
                13,
                11,
                12
            ],
            "answer": 12
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "13-6= ?",
            "options": [
                6,
                8,
                5,
                7
            ],
            "answer": 7
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "9+6= ?",
            "options": [
                14,
                13,
                16,
                15
            ],
            "answer": 15
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "10-8= ?",
            "options": [
                2,
                0,
                1,
                3
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "9-14= ?",
            "options": [
                -5,
                -7,
                -4,
                -6
            ],
            "answer": -5
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "5+13= ?",
            "options": [
                16,
                17,
                18,
                19
            ],
            "answer": 18
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 2": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "15+29= ?",
            "options": [
                45,
                44,
                40,
                43
            ],
            "answer": 44
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "19-18= ?",
            "options": [
                2,
                -1,
                1,
                4
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "12-11= ?",
            "options": [
                4,
                0,
                1,
                -1
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "8+18= ?",
            "options": [
                28,
                26,
                27,
                22
            ],
            "answer": 26
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "10-24= ?",
            "options": [
                -14,
                -12,
                -15,
                -18
            ],
            "answer": -14
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "27-29= ?",
            "options": [
                -1,
                -2,
                1,
                -4
            ],
            "answer": -2
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "11-12= ?",
            "options": [
                1,
                -5,
                2,
                -1
            ],
            "answer": -1
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "21-30= ?",
            "options": [
                -8,
                -10,
                -9,
                -7
            ],
            "answer": -9
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "22+16= ?",
            "options": [
                37,
                38,
                35,
                40
            ],
            "answer": 38
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "17+28= ?",
            "options": [
                44,
                47,
                41,
                45
            ],
            "answer": 45
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 3": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "35-32= ?",
            "options": [
                -3,
                6,
                3,
                2
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "44+29= ?",
            "options": [
                76,
                67,
                75,
                73
            ],
            "answer": 73
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "26+12= ?",
            "options": [
                41,
                39,
                38,
                42
            ],
            "answer": 38
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "40*34= ?",
            "options": [
                1362,
                1356,
                1360,
                1358
            ],
            "answer": 1360
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "34*38= ?",
            "options": [
                1292,
                1286,
                1289,
                1295
            ],
            "answer": 1292
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "13+28= ?",
            "options": [
                39,
                41,
                46,
                43
            ],
            "answer": 41
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "25-42= ?",
            "options": [
                -16,
                -20,
                -15,
                -17
            ],
            "answer": -17
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "47+15= ?",
            "options": [
                63,
                60,
                64,
                62
            ],
            "answer": 62
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "31+17= ?",
            "options": [
                52,
                43,
                50,
                48
            ],
            "answer": 48
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "22+22= ?",
            "options": [
                44,
                43,
                49,
                46
            ],
            "answer": 44
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 4": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "61*54= ?",
            "options": [
                3300,
                3290,
                3294,
                3289
            ],
            "answer": 3294
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "55*25= ?",
            "options": [
                1378,
                1375,
                1372,
                1373
            ],
            "answer": 1375
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "44-16= ?",
            "options": [
                27,
                22,
                34,
                28
            ],
            "answer": 28
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "57*35= ?",
            "options": [
                1997,
                1993,
                2002,
                1995
            ],
            "answer": 1995
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "53*40= ?",
            "options": [
                2118,
                2122,
                2112,
                2120
            ],
            "answer": 2120
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "53+30= ?",
            "options": [
                84,
                89,
                83,
                90
            ],
            "answer": 83
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "55*36= ?",
            "options": [
                1987,
                1973,
                1975,
                1980
            ],
            "answer": 1980
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "42*45= ?",
            "options": [
                1890,
                1893,
                1884,
                1897
            ],
            "answer": 1890
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "53+60= ?",
            "options": [
                113,
                108,
                117,
                107
            ],
            "answer": 113
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "58*62= ?",
            "options": [
                3593,
                3589,
                3590,
                3596
            ],
            "answer": 3596
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 5": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "38-31= ?",
            "options": [
                15,
                -1,
                9,
                7
            ],
            "answer": 7
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "27+22= ?",
            "options": [
                51,
                46,
                49,
                56
            ],
            "answer": 49
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "66-61= ?",
            "options": [
                -5,
                -3,
                1,
                5
            ],
            "answer": 5
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "47-56= ?",
            "options": [
                -17,
                -10,
                -9,
                -11
            ],
            "answer": -9
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "63-58= ?",
            "options": [
                6,
                5,
                11,
                12
            ],
            "answer": 5
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "63-68= ?",
            "options": [
                -12,
                -7,
                -2,
                -5
            ],
            "answer": -5
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "55-39= ?",
            "options": [
                14,
                16,
                20,
                24
            ],
            "answer": 16
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "39-53= ?",
            "options": [
                -5,
                -11,
                -21,
                -14
            ],
            "answer": -14
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "64+43= ?",
            "options": [
                108,
                107,
                109,
                104
            ],
            "answer": 107
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "79*28= ?",
            "options": [
                2217,
                2220,
                2221,
                2212
            ],
            "answer": 2212
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 6": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "50*76= ?",
            "options": [
                3790,
                3796,
                3800,
                3810
            ],
            "answer": 3800
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "83+89= ?",
            "options": [
                182,
                172,
                167,
                163
            ],
            "answer": 172
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "47+63= ?",
            "options": [
                110,
                99,
                105,
                115
            ],
            "answer": 110
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "90/67= ?",
            "options": [
                10.343283582089553,
                -0.6567164179104477,
                -4.656716417910448,
                1.3432835820895523
            ],
            "answer": 1.3432835820895523
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "61*69= ?",
            "options": [
                4209,
                4218,
                4219,
                4213
            ],
            "answer": 4209
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "79-26= ?",
            "options": [
                53,
                56,
                61,
                51
            ],
            "answer": 53
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "78-93= ?",
            "options": [
                -5,
                -7,
                -15,
                -20
            ],
            "answer": -15
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "76*79= ?",
            "options": [
                6004,
                5999,
                6011,
                6006
            ],
            "answer": 6004
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "42/61= ?",
            "options": [
                -11.311475409836065,
                -2.3114754098360657,
                0.6885245901639344,
                7.688524590163935
            ],
            "answer": 0.6885245901639344
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "87+92= ?",
            "options": [
                187,
                174,
                171,
                179
            ],
            "answer": 179
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 7": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "59/48= ?",
            "options": [
                1.2291666666666667,
                -1.7708333333333333,
                11.229166666666666,
                13.229166666666666
            ],
            "answer": 1.2291666666666667
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "49*29= ?",
            "options": [
                1421,
                1430,
                1413,
                1426
            ],
            "answer": 1421
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "82+55= ?",
            "options": [
                137,
                123,
                144,
                128
            ],
            "answer": 137
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "100+83= ?",
            "options": [
                179,
                183,
                193,
                195
            ],
            "answer": 183
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "91*87= ?",
            "options": [
                7917,
                7930,
                7907,
                7929
            ],
            "answer": 7917
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "101*64= ?",
            "options": [
                6452,
                6454,
                6464,
                6457
            ],
            "answer": 6464
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "100*52= ?",
            "options": [
                5200,
                5187,
                5212,
                5201
            ],
            "answer": 5200
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "101+95= ?",
            "options": [
                196,
                198,
                200,
                203
            ],
            "answer": 196
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "35-62= ?",
            "options": [
                -41,
                -28,
                -27,
                -16
            ],
            "answer": -27
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "36/64= ?",
            "options": [
                0.5625,
                -11.4375,
                -4.4375,
                -8.4375
            ],
            "answer": 0.5625
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 8": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "86+61= ?",
            "options": [
                133,
                137,
                147,
                149
            ],
            "answer": 147
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "91*124= ?",
            "options": [
                11273,
                11269,
                11284,
                11281
            ],
            "answer": 11284
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "48/55= ?",
            "options": [
                0.8727272727272727,
                -4.127272727272727,
                -5.127272727272727,
                3.8727272727272726
            ],
            "answer": 0.8727272727272727
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "44-67= ?",
            "options": [
                -9,
                -23,
                -34,
                -33
            ],
            "answer": -23
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "82-84= ?",
            "options": [
                -3,
                -6,
                -18,
                -2
            ],
            "answer": -2
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "113+75= ?",
            "options": [
                185,
                191,
                188,
                189
            ],
            "answer": 188
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "46*66= ?",
            "options": [
                3036,
                3044,
                3032,
                3037
            ],
            "answer": 3036
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "34-100= ?",
            "options": [
                -66,
                -81,
                -76,
                -70
            ],
            "answer": -66
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "95+105= ?",
            "options": [
                190,
                200,
                205,
                186
            ],
            "answer": 200
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "97/109= ?",
            "options": [
                1.889908256880734,
                7.889908256880734,
                0.8899082568807339,
                -1.110091743119266
            ],
            "answer": 0.8899082568807339
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 9": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "76/47= ?",
            "options": [
                -14.382978723404255,
                1.6170212765957446,
                -13.382978723404255,
                -7.382978723404255
            ],
            "answer": 1.6170212765957446
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "125+125= ?",
            "options": [
                250,
                266,
                260,
                249
            ],
            "answer": 250
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "73*45= ?",
            "options": [
                3288,
                3295,
                3285,
                3267
            ],
            "answer": 3285
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "79/72= ?",
            "options": [
                1.0972222222222223,
                17.09722222222222,
                5.097222222222222,
                16.09722222222222
            ],
            "answer": 1.0972222222222223
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "143/143= ?",
            "options": [
                2.0,
                11.0,
                1.0,
                5.0
            ],
            "answer": 1.0
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "58+126= ?",
            "options": [
                192,
                184,
                190,
                183
            ],
            "answer": 184
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "62/80= ?",
            "options": [
                9.775,
                16.775,
                -5.225,
                0.775
            ],
            "answer": 0.775
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "118*117= ?",
            "options": [
                13807,
                13811,
                13806,
                13789
            ],
            "answer": 13806
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "101/56= ?",
            "options": [
                1.8035714285714286,
                4.803571428571429,
                9.803571428571429,
                -1.1964285714285714
            ],
            "answer": 1.8035714285714286
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "106+54= ?",
            "options": [
                160,
                163,
                167,
                148
            ],
            "answer": 160
        }
    },
    "quiz math level 10": {
        "Q1": {
            "question": "84*72= ?",
            "options": [
                6029,
                6035,
                6048,
                6038
            ],
            "answer": 6048
        },
        "Q2": {
            "question": "45*106= ?",
            "options": [
                4770,
                4786,
                4765,
                4779
            ],
            "answer": 4770
        },
        "Q3": {
            "question": "98*67= ?",
            "options": [
                6563,
                6550,
                6566,
                6557
            ],
            "answer": 6566
        },
        "Q4": {
            "question": "141+77= ?",
            "options": [
                218,
                222,
                209,
                224
            ],
            "answer": 218
        },
        "Q5": {
            "question": "72*86= ?",
            "options": [
                6200,
                6207,
                6192,
                6179
            ],
            "answer": 6192
        },
        "Q6": {
            "question": "92-70= ?",
            "options": [
                17,
                40,
                22,
                27
            ],
            "answer": 22
        },
        "Q7": {
            "question": "82-77= ?",
            "options": [
                5,
                -14,
                -3,
                -5
            ],
            "answer": 5
        },
        "Q8": {
            "question": "144/154= ?",
            "options": [
                0.935064935064935,
                -15.064935064935066,
                -11.064935064935066,
                10.935064935064934
            ],
            "answer": 0.935064935064935
        },
        "Q9": {
            "question": "60*120= ?",
            "options": [
                7209,
                7200,
                7211,
                7197
            ],
            "answer": 7200
        },
        "Q10": {
            "question": "73+131= ?",
            "options": [
                218,
                207,
                195,
                204
            ],
            "answer": 204
        }
    }
}